[{"answer": " Hi, Diana.  Please come in and have a seat", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hi, Diana.  Please come in and have a seat", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Hows everything going?  Everything OK in your department", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Things in the department are going well.  I did want to talk to you about my jo", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hows everything going?  Everything OK in your department", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Sure.  Whats up", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Things in the department are going well.  I did want to talk to you about my jo", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": "Well, Ive recently interviewed with some different companies and one ha", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Sure.  Whats up", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": "Oh.  I didnt know that.  You know, Diana, we really value you here as a", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Well, Ive recently interviewed with some different companies and one ha", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Thank you.  I appreciate that", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Oh.  I didnt know that.  You know, Diana, we really value you here as a", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Are you unhappy with the position youre in or with some aspect of th", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Thank you.  I appreciate that", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " No, its nothing like that.  I really enjoy my work here.  Ive just been finding i", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Are you unhappy with the position youre in or with some aspect of th", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Oh, I see", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 43, "question": " No, its nothing like that.  I really enjoy my work here.  Ive just been finding i", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": "If I didnt like this company, it would be an easy decision.  But, I do really like i", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Oh, I see", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Well, I dont know about that.  Id have to look at the budget and check with th", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 49, "question": "If I didnt like this company, it would be an easy decision.  But, I do really like i", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Well, I dont know about that.  Id have to look at the budget and check with th", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": "Ill need to discuss with them about the work youve been doing in the position", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 54, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Yes, I can.  Actually, Ive taken on a lot of new responsibilities over the last year", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Ill need to discuss with them about the work youve been doing in the position", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Yes, I can.  Actually, Ive taken on a lot of new responsibilities over the last year", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Also, since Greg left, Ive taken on all of his job responsibilities.  Since no on", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 64, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " It does sound like youve taken on a lot of new responsibilities and show", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Also, since Greg left, Ive taken on all of his job responsibilities.  Since no on", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Not to toot my own horn, but I do believe that the department would suffer if ", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 75, "question": " It does sound like youve taken on a lot of new responsibilities and show", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " I agree with you.  It would be a big loss for the department to see you go", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Not to toot my own horn, but I do believe that the department would suffer if ", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 78, "question": " I agree with you.  It would be a big loss for the department to see you go", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Heres what I can do.  Let me talk to some people here at the company and Il", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Yes, definitely", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Heres what I can do.  Let me talk to some people here at the company and Il", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " OK.  Ill do that and hopefully have an answer for you by the end of the week", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Yes, definitely", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Yes, that sounds fine.  I dont need to let the other company know my decisio", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 89, "question": " OK.  Ill do that and hopefully have an answer for you by the end of the week", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Great.  Ill definitely have an answer for you by then", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Yes, that sounds fine.  I dont need to let the other company know my decisio", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Thank you, Sandy.  I really appreciate it", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Great.  Ill definitely have an answer for you by then", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  I hope we get to see you around for years to come", "docId": "03-07", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Thank you, Sandy.  I really appreciate it", "qSentId": 96}]
